Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG 37.4
New York University Archives
- Series II: Seminars, Lectures and Events
  - Theater Criticism - Tom Bishop, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lewis Thomas "Some New Agendas for Science", undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273477
  - Translation Seminar, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Travel Literature Seminar, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Urban Culture Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Urban Culture Seminar Budget, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Urban Commercial Culture, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Utopianism, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Vladimir Voinovich "Conversation on Writing & Politics", undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Edmund White "A Boy's Own Story" Book Party, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Edmund White "Trios" Performance, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Women Writing Women's Lives - Ann Snitow, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Women Writing Women's Lives - Readings, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The World of Goods (Mary Douglas) Colloquium, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    barcode#:31142042273485
  - Writing & Censorship Conference, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Writing & Censorship Conference - Correspondence, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Eugenia Zukerman/Anthony Newman Concert, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Cassette Tapes, 1974-2005
    - Richard Sennett, 27-Sep-74 (Box 32a, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273501
    - Richard Sennett, Wellfleet Conference, 21-Aug-76 (Box 32a, Folder 2)
    - Richard Sennett, "Broadband" ABC Radio, 4/4/1978 (Box 32a, Folder 3)
    - Doing Justice With Bakke Tape 1, 8-Jun-98 (Box 32a, Folder 4)
    - Doing Justice With Bakke Tape 2, 8-Jun-98 (Box 32a, Folder 5)
    - Roland Barthes - dialogue from videotape Tape 1, 7-Nov-78; RG37.4-JL-1 (Box 32a, Folder 6)
      CD of audio cassette on-site, box 77
    - Roland Barthes - dialogue from videotape Tape 2, 7-Nov-78; RG37.4-JL-2 (Box 32a, Folder 7)
    - Charles Rosen, Memory in Romantic Song Cycles, Parts I and II, 27-Oct-78; RG37.4-JL-3 (Box 32a, Folder 8)
    - Charles Rosen, Memory in Romantic Song Cycles, Part III, 27-Oct-78; RG37.4-JL-4 (Box 32a, Folder 9)
    - V.S. Naipaul Tape 1, 4-Apr-79; RG37.4-JL-5 (Box 32a, Folder 10)
    - V.S. Naipaul Tape 2, 4-Apr-79; RG37.4-JL-6 (Box 32a, Folder 11)
    - Stephen Spender, 24-Oct-80; RG37.4-JL-7 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273519
    - V.S. Naipaul and Richard Sennett, 11-Nov-80; RG37.4-JL-8 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett, "Sexuality and Solitude", 31-Oct-80; RG37.4-JL-9 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Culture of Cities Seminar, 13-Feb-81 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Sean Wilenty, Comparative Cultural Studies, 20-Feb-81 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Maynard Solomon, Biography Seminar, 24-Feb-81 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Jurgen Habermas, After Postmodernity Lecture, 6-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, "On Writing and Politics", 11-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Aileen Ward, Biography Seminar "Keats and Identity" no. 6, 17-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Bernard Gifford, 20-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - McLaughlin, Fundamentalism Tape 1, 20-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 2, 21-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 3, 21-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 4, 21-Mar-81 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Session 1, 23-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273527
    - Communism Session 2, 23-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Bill Taylor, Culture of Cities, "Age of Innocence" Tape 1, 27-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Bill Taylor, Culture of Cities, "Age of Innocence" Tape 2, 27-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Aileen Ward on Blake, 27-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Neier, Sontag, Sennett, Reiff, Straus, White, Cohen, Padilla - Seminar on Communism, 30-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Fundamentalism Tape 5, 31-Mar-81 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Justin Kaplan Luncheon, 3-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 1, 6-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 2, 6-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 1, 13-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Susan Sontag, "On Communism" Tape 2, 13-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Anthony Vidler, Culture of Cities Tape 1, 17-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Anthony Vidler, Culture of Cities Tape 2, 17-Apr-81 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Ronald Dworkin, 17-Mar-81 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273535
    - Communism and the Intellectual, 4-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Susan Sontag (back from China), "On Communism" Tape 1, 4-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Culture of Cities ?, 8-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Patrizia Lombardo and Carl Schorske, Comaparative Cultural Studies Tape 1, 12-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Patrizia Lombardo and Carl Schorske, Comaparative Cultural Studies Tape 2, 12-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - John Mason, Faurisson, 13-May-81 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture Tape 1, 29-Jul-81 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture Tape 2, 29-Jul-81 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 12-Aug-81 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 19-Aug- 81 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Todd Gitlin, Media and Popular Culture, 26-Aug-81 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - E. Kendall on Tchaikovsky Festival, 2-Oct-81 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273543
    - Todd Gitlin on Nuclear Proliferation, 8-Oct-81 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Fracois Furet on Tocqueville, 16-Oct-81 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Victor Navasky, "The Writers Congress", 23-Oct-81 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Professor Edel, Biography, 30-Oct-81 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Edmund White, Taste - Sei Shonagan, 11-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Philipe Roget on Common Sense, 6-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - E. Badinter, Fellows Lunch, 6-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Aryeh Neier on School Censorship, "Island Trees", 13-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Taste -Richard Howard on Baudelaire Tape 1, 19-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Taste -Richard Howard on Baudelaire Tape 2, 19-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - E. Holtzman on Kings City D.A., 20-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Bender and William Taylor - New York Symposium, 20-Nov-81 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Taste - Lord Berners, 2-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273550
    - New Right Tape 1, 5-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - New Right Tape 2, 5-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - New Right Tape 3, 5-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - New Right Tape 4, 5-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - New Right Tape 5, 5-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Architecture in New York Colloquium, 9-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Jarek Anders, Writing and Politics in Poland, 10-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Harry Levin, 11-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Ewa Kuryluk, 25-Mar-81 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Discussion on Polish Crisis, 18-Dec-81 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Sipho Sepamla, Fellows Lunch, 8-Jan-82 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Seminar, 21 Jan 1982 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Beard Conference Tape 1, 22-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273568
    - Beard Conference Tape 2, 22-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Beard Conference Tape 3, 22-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Beard Conference Tape 4, 22-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Richard Sennett, Democracy and Urban Form, 26-Feb-82 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Sex, Genders and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 28-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Allen Hunter on the New Right, 29-Jan-82 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 1, 11-Feb-82 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 2, 11-Feb-82 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Defert Lunch, 12-Feb-82 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Seminar, 25-Feb-82 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - John Leonard, Censorship Seminar, 11-Mar-82 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 1, 12-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273576
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 2, 12-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Linda Nochlin, Problems in Biography of Artists, 19-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - New Right Seminar 1, 20-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - New Right Seminar 2, 20-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - New Right Seminar 3, 20-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Monique Wittig, 26-Mar-82 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Tomas Venclova, Censorship Seminar, 1-Apr-82 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Edmund White, Trios, 19-Apr-82 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Bob Darnton, Censorship Seminar, 22-Apr-82 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Moshe Safdie Lecture, 25-Apr-82 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Censorship Seminar - Pornography, 13-May-82 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273584
    - Women, War and Feminism, 14-May-82 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ewa Kuryluk Luncheon, 28-May-82 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - H. Gans, Censorship Seminar "Self-Censorship", 4-Jun-82 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Gyorgy Bence "Independent Thought in Hungary", 12-Jul-82 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 1, 13-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273592
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 2, 20-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, On Borges, 24-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 1, 24-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 24-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - New Right Tape 2, 25-Sep-82 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 4-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 1, 5-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 2, 5-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Abel Decaux. Debussy - Chansons de Bilitis, 11-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 11-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence Pitkethly, Visual History, 14-Oct-83 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Nadine Gordimer, Fellows Lunch, 15-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Richard Howard, 18-Oct-82 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City, 19-Oct-82 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273600
    - Nicholas Wahl Tape 2, 22-Oct-82 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 25-Oct-82 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - T. Spires J.Coleman, Borges Seminar, 27-Oct-82 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Judith Wexler, 29-Oct-82 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 1-Nov-82 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - T. Nagel, The Mind-Body Problem, 5-Nov-82 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Charles Halpern, CUNY Queens School of Law, 12-Nov-82 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 1, 6-Nov-82 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Amartya Sen Lunch Tape 2, 16-Nov-82 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 1, 3-Dec-82 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 3-Dec-82 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 1, 14-Dec-82 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 2, 14-Dec-82 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 3, 14-Dec-82 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273618
    - George Soros, 10-Dec-82 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture, 17-Dec-82 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - William Leach, Sexuality and Consumerism, 14-Jan-83 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Richard Howard, Ante-Modernism, 21-Jan-83 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Ante-Modernism, 21-Jan-83 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - George Soros, International Financial Crisis, 4-Feb-83 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Richard Martin, Consumer culture - Fashion, 25-Feb-83 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Joan Wallach Scott, Gender and Work, 25-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Brodsky, Heaney, Walcott - Fellows Lunch, 4-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Jerome bruner Lunch - On Language, 11-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Richard Sennett, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Promiscuity, 11-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Workplace Seminar Tape 1, 15-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Workplace Seminar Tape 2, 15-Mar-83 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Aryeh Neier on Human Rights, 18-Mar-83 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273626
    - Anti-Modernism and Modernism, 25-Mar-83 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Jackson Lears, Advertising and Consumer Culture, 25-Mar-83 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Jackson Lears, Advertising and Consumer Culture, 25-Mar-83 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Italo Calvino Lunch, 1-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Hatch/Sassen-Koob, 6-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Searle, Putnam, Boyd, 8-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Haskell, 15-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Confessions of an Activist Mogul, 21-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sharon Thompson, Teenage Girls and Sexuality, 22-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Sharon Thompson, Teenage Girls and Sexuality, 22-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Stankiewicz Lunch, 29-Apr-83 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Luisa Velenzuela, Politics in Argentina, 20-May-83 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Hatch Tape 2, 8-Jun-83 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Hatch Tape 3, 8-Jun-83 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Derek Walcott, Narrative Seminar, 6-May-83 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273634
    - T. Kaplan, "The Left's Influence of Catholics", 30-Sep-83 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Sir Stuart Hampshire, 6-Oct-83 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Sir Stuart Hampshire, "History of Conflict", 7-Oct-83 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - A Tribute to W.H. Auden, Guggenheim Museum, 18-Oct-83 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Frank Kermode Lunch, Biblical Interpretation, 28-Oct-83 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Noel Annan, "How Should We Direct Shakespeare", 10-Oct-83 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, 14-Nov-83 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Richard Howard Lunch, on Gide, 18-Nov-83 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, 30-Nov-83 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Natalie Zemon Davis, Fellows Lunch, 2-Dec-83 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - William Weaver, "Verdi's Taste", 8-Dec-83 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - William Weaver, "Verdi's Taste", 9-Dec-83 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Friday Lunch/ Program Committee, 11-Jan-84 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - John Guare and Peter Brooks, Narrative Seminar, 8-Jan-84 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Richard Sennett, The Decline of Political Fiction, 20-Jan-84 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273642
    - Stan Eckstut, Learning from New York City, 10-Feb-84 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Yehudi Menuhin Lecture, 14-Feb-84 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - J. Hillis Miller Literary Criticism and Verification, 24-Feb-84 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Quentin Anderson, "Two Responses to a Consumer World", 2-Mar-84 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Alfred Kazin Lunch, 22-Mar-84 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Aryeh Neier Lunch, "Human Rights Abuses in South America", 23-Mar-84 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - George Konrad Lunch, "The Dilemmas of a New Novel", 30-Mar-84 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - David Reiff, Translation Seminar, 3-Apr-84 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Bill Leach Lunch, "Color, Glass and Light in New York City Department Stores", 6-Apr-84 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Richard Sennett, Narrative Seminar, 15-Apr-83 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Translation Seminar, 16-Apr-84 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - David Reiff, Translation Seminar, 16-Apr-84 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - David Kalstone, Narrating and Describing, 11-May-84 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - David Kalstone, Narrating and Describing, 11-May-84 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Maurice Berger, "The Empty Frame: Pictorial Realism", 18-May-84 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - R. Howard, Translation Seminar, 18-May-84 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Carol Smith Rosenberg, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - The Body Politic, 12-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273659
    - Father Ong, Institute Lunch, 12-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Jerome Bruner Lunch, Narrative and Paradigmatic Modes, 19-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Jerome Bruner and Richard Howard, Narrative Seminar, 23-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Sally Stein, Gender and Consumerism - Ladies Home Journal, 26-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Peter Buckley, Theatre and the Public, 26-Oct-84 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Tom Bishop, Narrative Seminar, 6-Nov-84 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Eric Hobsbawm, Literacy and the Tower of Babel, 9-Nov-84 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Lourdes Aguello and Ruby Rich, Sex and Gender - Repression of Homosexuality in Cuba, 9-Nov-84 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Aryeh Neier, Friday Lunch, 16-Nov-84 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Narrative Seminar, 11-Dec-84 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - E.L. Doctorow, 18-Jan-85 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Oliver Sacks, Clinical Biography, 22-Jan-85 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, Foreign Investments in the U.S., 25-Jan-85 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - John Coleman, Narrative Coleman, 5-Feb-85 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273667
    - Thomas Bishop, Performance to Text, 15-Feb-85 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - David Reiff and Ted Mooney, Travel, 19-Feb-85 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Vicki Hearne, Tracking Dogs and Traces of Speech, 22-Feb-85 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Carol Gilligan, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 15-Mar-85 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Galway Kinnell, Problems of Writing, 1-Mar-85 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Atina Grossman, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 29-Mar-85 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Emily Honig and Gail Hershatter, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 12-Apr-85 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Tony Quinton Lunch, 19-Apr-85 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Betty Fussell, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - on Cookbooks and Food, 26-Apr-85 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Leo Bersani, 2-May-85 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Leo Bersani - Follow-up lecture, 3-May-85 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Lisa Duggan, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 10-May-85 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Faye Ginsburg, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Right to Life Women, 24-May-85 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Nicholas Wahl, Friday Lunch - "Kundera's Europe: The Illusion of Westernity", 11-Nov-85 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273675
    - Chris Stansall, Sex - Gender, 11-Oct-85 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Bert Hansen, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 25-Oct-85 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Michael Scammel, Emigration of the Arts from the Soviet Union, 25-Oct-85 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Mark Girouard, To See and Be Seen Tape 1, 31-Oct-85 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Mark Girouard, To See and Be Seen Tape 2, 31-Oct-85 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Mark Girouard Follow-up Lecture, 1-Nov-85 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - George Chauncey II, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Sex Panics, 1-Nov-85 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Jeff Weinstein and Betty Fussel, Sex, Gender, 22-Nov-85 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, Argentina, Cannibals and Poets, 6-Dec-85 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Kate Ellis, Sex, Gender and Consumerism- Eating Disorders, 6-Dec-85 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumerism, "The Auto-Eroticism of Driving", 20-Dec-85 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Peggy Davis, "Watching Judges Make the Law", 31-Dec-85 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Breyten Breytenbach, Friday Lunch - New Poems, 17-Jan-86 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273683
    - Miriam Hansen, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - On Valentino, 31-Jan-86 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Bender, Lunch, 31-Jan-86 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Richard Sennett, Lunch - Reading from his new novel, 14-Feb-86 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Anthony Heilbut, culture and Economics, 21-Feb-86 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Mary Nash, Lunch - Spanish and Portuguese, 7-Mar-86 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - S. Bowles, American Culture, 21-Mar-86 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - John Coleman, Friday Lunch - Thinking About Singing, 4-Apr-86 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Eugenia Zukerman, Friday Lunch - For Flute Only, 18-Apr-86 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - M. Sinha, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 16-May-85 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Judy Walkowitz, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Victorian Melodrama, 30-May-86 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Richard Poirier, 11-Oct-86 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273691
    - Kate Stimpson, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Kate Stimpson on Representation, 24-Oct-86 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Aryeh Neier, 25-Oct-86 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Gerald Holton, Nov-86 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Laura Mulvey, Sex, Genderr and Consumerism, 7-Nov-86 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Roger Strauss Lunch, Frankfurt Book Fair, 7-Nov-86 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Dan Czitrom, 21-Nov-86 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Commercial Culture Seminar, 5-Dec-86 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Holton, Donoghue, bruner, 8-Dec-86 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Question of Progress in Science and the Humanities Tape II, 8-Dec-86 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Peter Buckley, 30-Jan-87 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Oliver Sacks on Darwin, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Inventing Times Square, Developing A Place, 28-Oct-88 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273709
    - "I Giullari di Piazza", "Dea Fortuna" Demo Tape, 9-Dec-88 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Katha Pollitt, 3-Mar-89 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Senelick, 3-Mar-89 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 1, 3-Mar-89 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 2, 3-Mar-89 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 3, 3-Mar-89 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Snow Dining Room Tape 1, 14-Apr-89 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Snow Dining Room Tape 1, 14-Apr-89 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Steering Committee Meeting, 29-Apr-89 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/3, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273717
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/3, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 3/3, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 21-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/3, 22-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 23-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 23-Mar-91 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Michael Wood, "On a Sentence By Proust" Tape 1, 15-Oct-93 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273725
    - Michael Wood, "On a Sentence By Proust" Tape 2, 15-Oct-93 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - A. Richard Turner, Adam Gopnik, "Art History: The Last Press of the Grape?" Tape 1, )ct 22, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - A. Richard Turner, Adam Gopnik, "Art History: The Last Press of the Grape?" Tape 2, )ct 22, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Ronald Dworkin, "Rationing, Justice and the Clinton Health Care Plan", 5-Nov-93 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Eva Hoffman, "Exit Into History: A Journey Through the New Eastern Europe", 12-Nov-93 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Martha Nussbaum, "Platonic Love and Colorado Law", 19-Nov-93 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Bawer and Paul Berman, "A Dialogue About Gay History", 18-Feb-94 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Lucy McDiarmid, "Roger Casement and Modern Irish Memory", 4-Mar-94 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Lucy McDiarmid, "Roger Casement and Modern Irish Memory" - Copy, 4-Mar-94 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Andrew Delbanco at Deutsches Haus - master, 25-Mar-94 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273733
    - Andrew Delbanco at Deutsches Haus - copy, 25-Mar-94 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Dennis Hollier at Deutsches Haus - master, 1-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Dennis Hollier at Deutsches Haus - copy, 1-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Francesca Dow at Deutsches Haus, 8-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Alfred Kazin, at Deutsches Haus, 15-Apr-94 (Box 56, Folder 6)